chrisvicmall.com 2013-12-27

# Privacy Policy ChrisvicMall

Your privacy is very important to us.This Privacy Policy is to ensure that your privacy is protected while using our site. Please make sure to read the Site's [Terms & Conditions](http://chrisvicmall.com/faqs/terms-and-conditions.html) as well. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

We may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where you are invited to volunteer such information, including, but not limited to, when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number.

### Third Party Ads

We use third party vendors, including Google,to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your interests in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

### What Do We Use Your Information For?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience, improve our website, improve customer service, process transactions, send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### Do We Disclose Information To Third Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information, except to provide products or services you've requested. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

### Third Parties Links

Chrisvicmall.com may contain links to third party sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Acceptance of Privacy Statement

Your use of our website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement and the Terms and Conditions. By using our site, you are accepting the practices set out in this privacy policy and our [terms & services](http://chrisvicmall.com/faqs/terms-and-conditions.html). We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of our website following posting of the updated privacy statement will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
